## Rodolfo Jahaziel Galván Martínez

rj@rjgalvan.com | <u>www.rjgalvan.com</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>GitHub</u>

Austin, TX

## **Profile**

Having had 8+ years of experience in computer science with a certification in full-stack web development and recent experience in entrepreneurship and product management, I can introduce a unique blend of both to develop and/or lead a dev team to success.

## **Work Experience**

PelotonU September 2019 - Present

Recruitment Coordinator

Austin, TX

 Responsible for developing a three-pronged strategy to build capacity for the Advising team at PelotonU and ensure success in student enrollment.

Codigo Austin August 2018 - Present

Co-founder, CEO, Instructor

Austin, TX

 Founded and runs Codigo Austin: a non-profit organization that promotes STEM fields to underserved students by creating connections through mentoring, exposure, and involvement.

Gold's Gym July 2018 - April 2019

Sales & Memberships

Austin, TX

- Reached out to potential gym members through the phone, email, or in person.
- Schedule meetings with potential members to help them reach their fitness goals. This job requires interaction with systems such as Salesforce.

Contract 2017 - Present

Freelance Web Developer & Technology Adviser

Austin, TX

- Built websites from the bottom up for various clients including Amparo Garcia-Crow.
- Advised clients on the technology and methods they use with their various technologies.

OnRamp Summer 2016

Marketing and Operations Intern

Austin, TX

OnRamp is a small data hosting company in Austin Texas that specializes in hybridity between cloud and colocation.

- Worked with WordPress cms, javascript/jquery/ajax, HTML, and CSS to create an online job application form.
  - Worked with Python, CakePHP, MySQL, Linux distros, and physical servers.

Whole Foods Global Summer 2015

Solution Architecture Intern

Austin, TX

- Helped create solution diagrams for point of sales.
- Used Python to help with data retrieval.
- Collaboratively studied a business case. Data modeling help.

Towne Park October 2015 - 2017

Staff Supervisor

Austin, TX

Lead for valet and bellman services at the Austin downtown Marriott.

Silicon Laboratories Summer 2014

Electrical Engineering Intern

Austin, TX

 $\bullet \qquad \text{Learned basic circuits, dipole antennas, digital design, statistics, programming, and logic gates.} \\$ 

**Education** 

Product Management Certification at The University of Texas at Austin

January 2020- January 2021

Associates in General Studies with a focus in Business at Southern New Hampshire University

March 2019-April 2020

Full Stack Javascript Web Development Certification at Austin Coding Academy

June 2019-April 2020

Computer Engineering at Austin Community College

2015 - 2018

**Voluntary Work** 

**Explore Austin** Board of Directors serving on the Programs and Board Governance Committees

October 2018-Present

Skills

- -Programming (OOP, Functional & Procedural)
- -Fluent in Spanish and English; Intermediate Portuguese
- -Full Stack Web Development (Node, JSX, SQL, React, Redux, etc.)